Finding Aid for the Edward Huntsman-Trout Papers LSC.1186
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Client
  - Client: Meighan., Garden., August 1941; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Client: Mendelsohn., Residence., April 1955-June 1956; 5 items. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Client: Merriwether., Residence., October 1936; 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Client: Mesmer., January 1942.; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Client: Metropolitan Bank, Los Angeles., October 1962.; 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Client: Meyer., Grounds., October-December 1956; 7 items. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Client: Miller, A., Residence., July 1937-September 1938; 21 item. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Client: Miller, A., Grounds., March 1945; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Client: Miller, P. (photographs). Residence., 15 items. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Client: Mock., Grounds., December 1952; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Client: Model of modern house. Polaroid photographs., 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Client: Monrovia., 2 items. (Box 83)
  - Client: Montag., Residence., July 1956; 9 items. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Client: Morris., Garden., October-December 1951; 4 items. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Client: Mosher., Grounds., April-July 1953; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Client: Moulton., Additions., August 1969-January 1970; 3 items. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence (Leona)., July 1946-February 1951; 17 items. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Small photographs., 5 items. (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Additions., October 1945-January 1947; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Pool and court., September 1946-December 1948; 23 items. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Pool and court., March 1948-June 1949; 17 items. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Pool and court., October 1947-October 1948; 15 items. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 2 items. (Box __)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Photographs - W.M. Clarke (2 dam.)., 1930; 7 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 10 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 10 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 10 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 10 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Residence., 10 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., December 1928-May 1929; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., October-December 1928; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., September 1928-October 1929; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., August 1928, n.d.; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., July 1928, n.d.; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., July-October 1928; 10 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., September 1929-March 1930; 10 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., September 1930-May 1936; 8 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., April 1934-June 1941; 6 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., June 1930-March 1934; 10 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., December 1929-March 1930; 10 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Residence., March-May 1930; 10 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Hillside garden., July 1953-October 1954; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey., Planting notes., December 12, 1930; 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Photographs by W.M. Clarke., 10 items. (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey. Estate., 9 items. (Box 59)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey S. Drawing on board and Mott photo., 2 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Mudd, Harvey(?). Photographs., 6 items. (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Client: Mudd, Henry., Ranch., June-December 1950; 10 items. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Client: Mudd, Mrs., Alterations., June 1955-February 1956; 5 items. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Client: Mudd, Mrs., Gates., February-April 1957; 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Client: Mudd. H.S. Photographs., 6 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Mullen and Bluett, Los Angeles., March 1949.; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Client: Murphy., Garden., August 1937; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Client: Myers., Residence., May 1946; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Client: Neal, P., Residence., September-October 1937; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Client: Neal. R. Garage., 8 items. (Box __)
  - Client: Neblett. (Box 124)
  - Client: Neblett., Additions., December 1966-March 1968; 64 items. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Client: Neblett., Gate., March 1971; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Client: Neff., Residence., August 1967-September 1970; 4 items. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Client: Noll., Residence., November 1949-February 1950; 5 items. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Client: O'Brien., Garden., December 1941; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Client: O'Melveney., Residence., August 1933; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Client: Observation Nursery School, Los Angeles., June 1956.; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Client: Olmsted, Frederick Law., Huntsman-Trout ASLA certificate., 1920; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Client: Outdoor wedding. Photographs., 9 items. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Client: Pachappa School, Riverside., January 1953.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Client: Paley., Residence (one drawing encaps 142)., August-December 1935; 14 items. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Client: Paley., Residence., January-August 1936; 29 items. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Client: Paley. Residence (1 board)., 2 items. (Box 141)
  - Client: Paley. Residence (encapsulated drawing from Box 2)., 1 item. (Box 142)
  - Client: Paley. Residence (photos)., 24 items. (Box 142)
  - Client: Paley(?). Photographs., 18 items. (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Client: Palos Verdes. (Box 94)
  - Client: Panama., Residence., June 1957-April 1958; 9 items. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Client: Parkway Courts Motel, Hollywood., January-February 1949.; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Client: Paul., Garden., May-September 1941; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Client: Pavilion in woods, garden. Photographs., 9 items. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Client: Paving, wall, fence. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Client: Peabody. Photographs., 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Client: Peet, Elbert., Letter., July 16, 1949; 8 items. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Client: Peet, Elbert. (?) Map (photostat), overlay., 1947, 1949; 2 items. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Client: Pendleton. (Box 94)
  - Client: Pensick., Residence., June-September 1950; 3 items. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Client: Perry., Correspondence., February 1954; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Client: Pershing Square, Los Angeles., November 1950.; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Client: Pickfair., July-September 1941.; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Client: Pike., Residence., October 1948-September 1949; 10 items. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Client: Pike., Pool., February 1951; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Client: Pike., Additions., December 1952-January 1953; 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Client: Pike., Additions, Palm Springs., December 1955; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Client: Pine., Grounds., September 1956-March 1957; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Client: Pinkham., Residence., December 1923-April 1924; 5 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Pinkham., Residence, Carpinteria., April-June 1955; 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Client: Pinkham., Site, Beverly Hills., May 1955; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Client: Pinkham., Correspondence., May-June 1955; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Client: Pinkham., Mounted small photographs., August 1925; 5 items. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Client: Pinkham. Mounted small photographs., 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Client: Pinkham. Estate., 3 items. (Box 69)
  - Client: Pioneer Electronics Corporation, West Los Angeles., September 1953.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Client: Poe. (Box 131)
  - Client: Poe., Additions., November 1969-May 1970; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Client: Poe., Correspondence, accounts., December 1969-July 1970; 71 item. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Client: Polito., Garden., April 1953; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Client: Polito., Garden - bill and memo., July 1953; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Client: Polson., Residence., October 1958-October 1959; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Client: Ponty. Residence., 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Client: Ponty., Residence., February-August 1951; 12 items. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Client: Pool house, garden. Photographs, proof strips., 9 items. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Client: Potted plant. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Client: Pringle., Residence., November 1937-July 1938; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Client: Rancho model house., June-July 1947.; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Client: Raymond., Ground alterations., September-October 1967; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Client: Reafsnyder., Grounds., June-August 1954; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Client: Reeder., Grounds., February-May 1970; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Client: Reeder., Correspondence, accounts., February-June 1970; 11 item. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Client: Rex. (Box 118)
  - Client: Rex., Ranch., September 1964; 7 items. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Client: Rex., Sketches, correspondence, invoices., July 1964-August 1972, n.d.; 80 items. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Client: Richards., Residence., January-June 1942; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Client: Rieber., Grounds., October 1955; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Client: Rigby., Grounds., December 1958-December 1959; 6 items. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Client: Ripley. Residence., 2 items. (Box 81)
  - Client: Riverside Cement Company, Crestmore., January 1957.; 10 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Client: Riverside County Juvenile Hall., June 1952.; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Client: Road grading, house construction. Photographs (small proofs)., 16 items. (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Client: Robbins. Grounds., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Client: Robbins., Residence., January-February 1960; 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Client: Robbins, Jr., Terrace., May 1951; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Client: Rodesci. Residence., 5 items. (Box 78)
  - Client: Roen., Garden., May 1932; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Client: Rosenfeld., Residence., August 1965-January 1966; 3 items. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Client: Ross., Grounds., February-March 1946; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Client: Ross., Garden., December 1948-January 1949; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Client: Roth., Garden., July 1953-May 1954; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Client: Rothmund., Estate., May 1946-April 1947; 10 items. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Client: Rothmund., Grounds., October 1948-June 1949; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Client: Rothschild., Grounds., May 1961; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Client: Rounds - see also Baldwin(?) [identification unclear]. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Rounds - see also Baldwin? photographs [identification unclear]. (Box Unknown container 218 for instance of Client: Rounds - see also Baldwin? photographs [identification unclear].)
  - Client: Rubidoux High School, Riverside., September 1959-January 1960.; 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Client: Salsbury., Residence., May-June 1962; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Client: Salsbury. Residence., 1 item. (Box 64)
  - Client: Salvatori., Residence., October 1955; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Client: Salvatori., Residence, Bel-Air., February-April 1962; 6 items. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Client: Salvatori., Pool., May-June 1964; 17 items. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Client: Salvatori., Pool., June-July 1964; 18 items. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Client: Salvatori. Pool., 4 items. (Box 53)
  - Client: Salvatori., 2 items. (Box 68)
  - Client: Santa Ynez Inn, Los Angeles., May 1949.; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Client: Schenck., Residence., May 1939; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Client: Schertzinger. Photographs., 6 items. (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Client: Schneider., Residence., August-September 1951; 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Client: Schneider., Correspondence., June 1951; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Client: Schoenbrun., Residence., March-August 1940; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Client: Schuyler. Photographs., 6 items. (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Client: Schweppe., Residence., July 1933-January 1934; 3 items. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Client: Schweppe, R.J. (Box 90)
  - Client: Scott III., Residence., August 1956-June 1957; 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photograph - Robert C. Frampton., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs - Eckbo book., 17 items. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs - W.M. Clarke., 14 items. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs - enlargement. Earl V. Lewis., 13 items. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs of plans., 3 items. (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs by W.M. Clarke., 6 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Plan - Mott photograph (mounted)., 1 item. (Box 132)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs - Mott Studios., 6 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Folio with H. - T. label (ephemera). (Box 133)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 133)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., 9 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., May-October 1936; 10 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., March 1936-October 1941; 8 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., November 1932-February 1936; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., March 1930-May 1931; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., February 1928, n.d.; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., February-July 1928; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Original drawings., 8 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., April 1928-March 1934; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Original drawings., 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., August 1929-March 1930; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Original drawings., August 1928-August 1929; 10 items. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., [Presentation drawing(?) color]., 1 item. (Box 140)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Board., March 1936-October 1941; 1 item. (Box 142)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., East campus., April 1957-November 1960; 30 items. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., 11th Street entrance., June 1965; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Sketchbook, planting notebook., 1930s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Sketchbook, planting notebook., 1930s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Sketchbook, planting notebook., 1930s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Sketchbook, planting notebook., 1930s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Sketchbook, planting notebook., 1930s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Planting sketches (also Mudd, etc.)., ca. 1930; 8 items. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., Correspondence, redevelopment., November-December 1971; 6 items. (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Statement for Eckbo book., 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs of model, Mott Studios., 7 items. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Overhead view drawing (photograph)., 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Landscape plan overview (photo)., 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Small photographs, for Eckbo book(?)., 75 items. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Photographs?., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. The Oratory, mounted photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont. Small photographs., 9 items. (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., 6 items. (Box 43)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., 3 items. (Box 44)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont., 7 items. (Box 87)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont [change copy negative information]. Drawing (photo print and negative). (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Client: Scripps College, Claremont(?). Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Client: Scripps, Pomona, Mudd., Calendars, article., 1963-1966; 5 items. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr., Residence., January-June 1922; 4 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Mounted small photographs., 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Mounted photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Mounted photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Mounted photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Client: Seyler, Jr.(?). Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Client: Seymon., Residence., August 1946-November 1949; 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Client: Seymon., Addition., May 1954; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Client: Seymon. Property., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Client: Shapiro., Grounds., October 1960; 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Client: Shearer., Residence., November 1946; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Client: Sheats. Residence., 12 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Sheats., Residence., February 1962; 4 items. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Client: Sheehan., Residence., October 1941-March 1945; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Client: Sherwood., Residence., January 1962-May 1963; 14 items. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Client: Shuken, Jay M. (Box 123)
  - Client: Shuken, Jay M., Correspondence, invoices., April 1972-April 1974; 67 items. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Client: Shumway., Grounds., October 1970-February 1971; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Client: Shumway., Accounts., March-April 1971; 3 items. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Client: Shurtz., Residence., April-December 1951; 10 items. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Client: Simon., Alterations., October 1965-March 1967; 7 items. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Client: Simon., Alterations., March 1967-November 1969; 7 items. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Client: Simonson. (Box 130)
  - Client: Simonson, R.R., Letter, invoice., April 1973; 2 items. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Client: Siple. Residence., 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Client: Site plans. (Box 94)
  - Client: Sketches. (Box 90)
  - Client: Slag heap(?). Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Client: Slimard, Mr and Mrs W.J. Architectural plans. (Box 96)
  - Client: Smith., May 1958-May 1960.; 6 items. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Client: Spanish Colonial house, grounds. Photographs., 8 items. (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Client: Spanish Colonial revival house. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Client: Spanish Colonial revival house, under construction. Photographs., 7 items. (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Client: Spanish Colonial revival houses. Photographs., 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Client: Spear., Mounted small photographs., February 1925; 6 items. (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Client: Spears. Improvements - photographs., 3 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Spears., Residence., November 1925; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Sprague, Jr., Residence., December 1948-December 1949; 4 items. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Client: Sprague, Jr., Additions., July-September 1959; 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Client: Sprong., Residence., February 1950-June 1951; 6 items. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Client: St. Matthias Episcopal Church, Seaside., August 1957.; 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Client: Statue, photograph. Not Huntsman-Trout(?). (Box 142)
  - Client: Steele, Fletcher., Letter to Huntsman-Trout., August 12, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Client: Steele, Fletcher. Typed note (inactive mold). (Box 98)
  - Client: Steps, wall, entrance courts (site of wedding. Photographs., 11 item. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Client: Sterling., Pool., January 1950-January 1952; 14 items. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Client: Stevenson., Residence., June 1941-January 1942; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Client: Stoessel., Garden., September 1966-January 1967; 3 items. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Client: Stone river embankment. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Client: Stroud., Residence., February-April 1946; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Client: Sturdevant., Site., June 1959; 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Client: Sunset Lanai apartments, Los Angeles [West Hollywood]., May-July 1954.; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Client: Tahquitz Company, Palm Springs., November 1947-June 1948.; 20 items. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Client: Tahquitz Company, Palm Springs., Plot plans., September 1948-February 1949; 13 items. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Client: Taylor., Residence., February 1937; 3 items. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Client: Technicolor Corporation (Dr. Kalmus)., Bel-Air parking facilities., March 1952 -August 1953; 18 items. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Client: Terrace, garden path with fountain. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Client: Thatcher., Grounds., September 1961; 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Client: The Alhambra. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Client: Theodore Payne Foundation., Mailings., 1960s-1970s (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Client: Thorsch., Residence., August-November 1956; 16 items. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Client: Trousdale., Office., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Client: Trousdale., Ranch., March-October 1946; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Client: Trousdale., Residence., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Client: Trousdale., Westdale Homes., May-August 1947; 13 items. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Client: Trousdale., Estates., July-October 1955; 12 items. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Client: Trousdale., Site., November-December 1954; 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Client: Trousdale., South lot., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Client: Trousdale (photographs). Ranch., 5 items. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Client: Trowbridge., Garden., September 1940; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Client: Twaits., Residence., January 1946-May 1947; 10 items. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Client: Twentynine Palms. (Box 94)
  - Client: Ullman. (Box 112)
  - Client: Ungrouped photographs. Photographs., 17 items. (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Client: Unidentified - garden wall with boy playing pipes. Photograph - Mott Studios., 1 item. (Box 133)
  - Client: Unidentified - Spanish house exteriors, pictorialist style. Photographs - Mott Studios., 3 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Unidentified garden. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Client: Unidentified garden and garden house. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Client: Unidentified garden courtyard. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Client: Unidentified garden sketch. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Client: Unidentified garden, wall, ramada. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Client: Unidentified garden, wall, steps (Ronda steps). Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Client: Unidentified landscapes. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Client: University of California, Riverside., Residence hall site development., May 1964 (Box 36, Folder 7)